Hello hello and Gautameshwar and keep
creating the channel friends, in this we saw that the
stock market has finally broken its old all
time high and has shown a new desperate,
so in this I have divided the best of two bank
voids into two videos, the
first video in which we will identify such large
cap stocks which are currently
available at a good reasonable support level even after this breakup and the
second video in which we will talk about mid and small caps,
so this is the first video in which
we have discussed such fundamentalism last
episode 525 which can withdraw entry cash for your machine,
whatever
is available to you at a good valuation, which
festival you can buy, we will
discuss that in this video friends, if
you have not subscribed to the channel then do it now
and press the bell icon because
I keep updating my boss on such weekly basis, be stopped by
job and keep
sharing it with you, which can be of great
use, so without taking any more
fear, detested, so friends, our
last story  The first companies in the description of TCS are the
battle of companies like Tata Consultancy Services, updates, or that
cord
Shravan. I don't think it's appropriate here
because there won't be any Indian who does
n't know about this thing.
TCS is India's largest IT company
and along with being the largest IT company, it is also
India's largest employer, the largest
number four
company that improves the lives of Indians. So, a joint
IT company like TCS has a lot of competitive
advantages. In the IT sector, the business
company that I like the most is
TCS, and I have done different reasons. I
think that to acquire TCS, you
can first keep in mind the price in 2014, that is Rs. 2985-3050 or you
will see, its consolidation has been going on for many months,
Systems of Medicine has been going on for about five months
and
it always takes support around this range. So the first price
that you can keep in mind is
more than Rs. 120. The second price level, if you think
that  Although there has been a breakout in the market,
it has also been well supported, but
if you feel that the near term will remain for Bollywood, as long as
we talk about the second and third
quarter, then if any
near term body is formed, some
declines in the market, then 2750, 2850 are
different types of support levels from 2017 to 2030,
where it has taken support many times
and you can see many moving averages of this,
218, which has a very important
movie, is around 28 years of 0860
and hundreds of movies,
that too many times, you can see that we have
many passports with the moving average speed of ads, in that
also the value of the person is
coming around something, so
in the continuation of the phase, which we talked about earlier,
that support is found in it, but
he feels that you can get the opportunity to acquire teachers,
if you feel
more comfortable with whichever press statement from these two,
when this TCS
stock comes, then you  You can start your admission
but it is the biggest company in India. It is the
main square of India's largest party according to
market capitalization. One of the
last IT companies in India, so you
can keep TCS in your mind. Definitely these
companies are not stopped at, you can keep in mind
for long term examination and
vestiges. The next company in the general insurance
sector, India's market leader in the
private sector is itself, but it is also a
very strong company in the front arm of life
insurance. General insurance is the uber
insurance sector. You can share your views with us. Its immensity potential
in India is very under-pegged
market and future care needs of active people.
Your potential is quite good than the enemies.
Better fundamentalist company in the general
insurance sector in India, ICICI
Lombard, can
bring the first proposal to calculate this to 1314. From the
other, rather if you want to enter, then that
cross can bring the modern 1200 festival
splash in your life insurance sector.
If we talk about the private life insurance sector, then
I like the biggest one the most which is
worthy and different from this, its name is comparative
Analysis and Fundamental Rights of 1962
I will discuss in this video
why I like HDFC Life more than all my private companies but till
now I could have told you that the product quality is
so good, the financial year is good, it is a
well garment company, it belongs to the SSC
group, so it
needs representation in the market, people trust it, it has
quality from many fundamental attributes due to which I like this
lamp by
turning it around, like, comment, from the question asked in the Life Insurance Act, I can
say from the first point
Kunwarpal of 675, the second press level, if you
want to weight it, then it can be 5 and a half level,
although the health of life insurance does
not fall much, when there is a
decline in the stocks of the financial sector, then life insurance and general
insurance do not fall without currency
because when it is listed as worthless, the
share consistency of these keeps increasing, but if you
want to weight that factor, then you can
also use more than 5 and a half, i.e. 55075,
inside you can talk  It's amazing, form
next companies and although
in other centers but it is a giant year old company
in Hindustani, it is a child porn
related company in India
in the adventure chapter, the largest company in terms of
market capitalization in terms of
market share in terms of number of
products in terms of market. If we
talk about anything, then there is no
bigger company than Hindustani in India
and you will know Unilever Accuracy
Investment in Action,
its Indian subsidiary Hindustan
Unilever, we will talk about rice,
like comment, the first attempt
which you can keep in mind is 55031,
so the second reserve if you
want to make your million in this also and if you
feel that there is some dance address system,
consolidation is going on for many days,
you can also see that you have seen that the
price range of July-August 129 of last year is around July-August,
so you can understand how
big the consolidation has been going on for how long, there is
not much placement in its taste for many months, so if
you think that  If it can become a little more popular
then you can expect a wait of 2150 to 550 but
you can see it lightly. There is a lot of
growth in the movie which is between these two supports, so
admission can be started between those two and Port Louis, wherever you feel more comfortable,
but Hindustan Unilever is a very
smart company, you can check its written letters, there
is a function to check the market share,
check the market share,
which sector is the biggest company,
now go to any grocery store,
go to the store, do marketing on it,
there you will see
GTA five percent products actually
because in every market,
whether it is on the shoe, shot put, pressure cooker, top,
shampoo, detergent and any other product,
which is our daily life insurance,
Hindustan Unilever has created a huge market share in all those product ranges,
so it is a very good company, it depends,
after considering all these factors, if you feel that
Hindustan Unilever is suitable for your investment, then
Left, this is such a
price range which you can keep at home, the
next company is a big company in the important cheese
sector, but in the comment below, like
we talked about Hindustan Unilever,
many of its products were
caught in many market segments, but
if we talk about Britannia Industries, then
in the comment below, it is mentioned that
fractional biscuits, even some
dairy products, then in all these product ranges,
Vitamin E has understood, it has created a
very good reputation in the market, it has a
very good market share
and market share too, in this way,
Britannia Industries has
created a good name for itself in the product range at
this time and in the case of natural,
you can see this thing here
and then you are
getting it around the price range of last year's John Chudai in July 2017, you
can see how much
consolidation has happened in it, let's see how much admission
people are still getting the same prices, you are getting it
at a good discount from
its all-time high, it is around 14
thousand, so there  From here you can see that
you get at least 50% discount on protein, so how is it getting at a good discount,
still such a solid company,
such a motor company, it
is available to you on reservation at a good discount, so the
first festival of 3353 450 3550 3450, where
you can see the moving average
speed of many, many times this recipe has been supported to such an extent, then
definitely it is the
first president and keep in mind for
examination, Britannia Industries, the second
festival, if you want to see
such a huge decline,
songs like Britannia Industries come in the top usually, but
if it comes on this channel between 3600,
then 8 and even more out
money, for maximum volume, Britannia
Industries, the next company is a German company,
India Under-19 cricket, the
market leader of its sector, lower Indian
ethnic Swiss West companies, a
multinational company, we are talking about its Indian celebs in
India, for this look,
you can see its root
is the moving average.  On this, there
is a proposal of around 16000 to 16500 which
is very attractive, here you
can definitely initiate your admission,
if you want to wait a little or take a more
conservative approach then you
can fit the level of 15000 to 15500, there
admission of 20 can be started in a very aggressive channel,
from your company naukri.com, which you know, today
we are talking about it, this is also fundamentally
from the company, many such businesses perform well, for this I am
definitely aware of naukri.com, I have
also pinned it on the department portal, then there are many startups in
these that offer jobs in many ways in the metro,
so you can see the
fundamentals of this from its
director, he is also a very rapid investor, the
staff has
good stake in many businesses of his own blood,
so if you want to activate these for schools,
if you see the potential in it, then long term group
So politicians and gifted
abstainers can get good price of law center support
where you
can start depression at the minimum but if you
should wait a little as you see there is a
lot of quality stop, there is a lot of
momentum in it as you have also seen from the chart, so
if you want to wait a little then you
can update Pacific of 3536, if it
comes first according to that then definitely don't
support level at long term
investment for which naukri.com The next
company is another big IT company of India
TCS and Infosys, the tractors keep talking
in 2000, profile office point comes to
IT sector, but such technology is actually
jewellery from player electric, smaller
player than these two, smaller than TCS and Wipro,
but actually when we will do it
by making computers and those who bring it seriously,
very soon in this, many tractors of
service sectors of different sperm
market places are going to
see many of their parents complaining and
here we will do base quality comparison of parents,
contact Banaras  There are a
lot of stroke players of certain
industries, they should compete with each other
and see who comes out as the winner. So in this
we will examine IT
technologies in the IT sector, but right now
I can tell you that technology can
definitely you might also very from fear in the future
Biscuit Mandleshwar has very good
business management operations,
its corporate governance has been very good, its
sleep statement is also very good,
so I think this chapter note
scan definitely PM very from IT appeared that
you can keep unknown alarm
from the soil to update Infosys Technologies, the
first price change can be
that Big Boss Abhijit current price range is the
second price which can be paid
which is an important support level, the
next important support level is
complete license between 800 to 500 on WhatsApp,
definitely western wear, that
tractor president should update HCL
Technologies for long term is Russian m good
growth potential, one of the leading
companies in India in electrical statements
And if you talk about
consumer products of Decris Pimple, then the
name of Havells
definitely comes up there. You must have heard the name of this company.
Its products are very good
in the Kachighati market,
much better than the international market.
If you search for the biggest electrical company in India, then the
name of every 10 is there. If you look at the biggest
market complex, then I will tell you
that Havells has come out as a score of millet. You
can see that you had a lot of
consolidation for the first time. If you
show it to yourself, then through that means you
can update the traffic of 1000 rupees.
Speculations can be done there.
Secondly, if you want to wait,
you can see its data moving
average, there it is 811. So I think that
this leave 2981 today from the price. Western
wear look test for long term
investment. You can invest a little more there if in such a
way, you can invest in Hathras.
This has long-term potential. Long-term
goals scored in her, so this company is one of India
's leading housing finance companies.  The company HDFC
Limited Housing Development Finance
Corporation is the parent company of Ford
HDFC Bank, HDFC Life Insurance Corporation,
and two other companies like HDFC Bank and HDFC Life Insurance Corporation Limited, which have a very strange
problem. We are talking about HDFC
Limited selling 8 minutes of its services starting from 24 and 25 rupees, starting
from clothes at an attractive price.
However, if you want to wait a little, you
can see the dowry that Modi sent in the
films, then it is at an
attractive price of 1000 rupees per tractor at
Jabalpur station. But for the long term,
in HDFC Limited, till today, I have two or three pots
in our company Indraprastha Gas Limited. I especially like this company Indraprastha Gas Limited, which is a
Gujarat company, which has cardamom, more energy,
State Petroleum Limited, Metropolitan Joint Secretary,
and I also like Indraprastha Gas very much.
It operates in some areas of Delhi NCR, Haryana, etc.
Its focus is on those locations, the number
telecom is quite strong, the company updates are free, the
companies are quite big, the companies Andreas
that operate in, I think that for doing
8 minutes of IPL  475 Sarpanch and Principal
Candidate Starting Price Label President's
Day Special Many times in this support yaar juice
can be a good price payment for long term
examination in IPL
Srinagar I want to wait a little if
you feel that the market sentiment is a bit
bad, there could be some consolidation loss in the market,
then you
can wait more for IPL dreams, there
you will find it, many Agrasen Chowk can be
started but I have saluted it, there is a lot of
motors company, from company and seeds, that is,
city gas distribution companies,
one of my favorites and can be a good
investment for the long term, I think it
can be a very good investment, even now the
penetration of gas supply
is not very much in India and due to its environmental
clearance, when to do pollution, it makes sense to do
long-term goals and
Indore city gas distribution companies arise verbs from complaints
city gas
distribution, so I hope
friends what size we
discussed here, they discussed the price of these rotis  I
also discussed all their business a little bit, so you will benefit from it.
All these discussions can also be used
on rent for long term investment from
bulk. This is my hope and belief that all these will be
helpful for you all year long term.
Well, friends, this is today's video cassette
which is Knowledge Power Supreme. This channel
is commissioned to deliver the right information to you.
In the upcoming new videos, we will
discuss many international offices and I will keep bringing
useful collides and topics for you.
Similarly, we will keep discussing weekly market
updates and our views. We will
also keep discussing market situation. So,
definitely subscribe to our channel and become the
father of today. If you like today's video content, then
like the video. If
you think that this information
can help someone, then share it with your friends and
family members and
subscribe to the channel. We will see you in our next
video with discussion on more topics. Till then,
take care, see you soon.